Guide to the Andrea Callard Papers MSS.156
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: Video recordings
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - Flourescent/ Azalea, a film by Andrea Callard (2009 Restoration), 1976; ID: 156.166 (Case 156.0166)
      Currently available.
      Existence and Location of Copies
      .
      General note
      Format: DVD, color, sound
      Duration: 4 minutes
      Original format: Super 8mm film
    - 11 thru 12, a film by Andrea Callard (2009 Restoration), 1977; ID: 156.0158 (Case 156.0158)
      Duration: 00:11:00
      Original: Super 8mm film
    - [1]-- "11 thru 12" [2]-- "Mary Ann" [3]-- "Men In Orbit"; Co-laborative Projects June 4 Tape, [circa 1977-1980]; ID: 156.0149 (Case 156.0149)
      Duration: 01:00:32
      Original Format: 3/4" Umatic
    - Men in Orbit, fales_mss156_cuid_meninorbit/ (E-records fales_MSS156, E-records fales_mss156_cuid_meninorbit/)
  - Subseries B: Submasters - CLOSED
    CLOSED
    - Lost Shoe Blues, Flora Funera (for Battery Park City), 2011; cuid23198 (Box Shared Fales PM 8, Case 156.0176)
    - Fluorescent/Azalea, undated; cuid23199 (Box Shared Fales PM 8, Case 156.0165)
    - 11 Thru 12, undated; cuid23200 (Box Shared Fales PM 8, Case 156.0157)
    - 11 Thru 12, cuid23206 (Box Shared Fales PM 69, Case 156.0174)
  - Subseries C: Preservation Masters - CLOSED
    - "Fluorescent/Azalia", 2010-07-29; cuid23201 (Box Shared Fales PM 48, Case 156.0163)
    - Mary Ann, Men in Orbit, cuid23202 (Box Shared Fales PM 69, Case 156.0150)
    - Lost Shoe Blues, 2011-03-23; cuid23203 (Box Shared Fales PM 69, Case 156.0175)
    - "11 Thru 12", 2014-06-06; cuid23204 (Box Shared Fales PM 69, Case 156.0156)
    - Lost Shoe Blues, Flora Funera (for Battery Park City), cuid23205 (Box Shared Fales PM 69, Case 156.0174)
  - Subseries D: Video recordings
    - Title: [1]-- "11-12" [2]-- "Mary Ann" [3]-- "Men In Orbit", [circa 1977-1980]; cuid22926 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0001)
      Alternate title: Colaborative Projects June 4 Tape
      Credit info: [1]-- Andrea Callard [2]-- J. Holzer; J. Brettschneider [3]-- John Lurie
      Format: 3/4 in. Umatic
      Capacity: 60 minutes
      Annotations: Colaborative Projects June 4 Tape. 1.) "11-12" Andrea Callard 12 min. 2.) "Mary Ann" J. Holzer, J. Brettschneider 6 min. 3.) "Men In Orbit" John Lurie / 40 min.
      The "Men in Orbit" segment is available as high-resolution preservation master file. To request access to this file, email fales.library@nyu.edu.
    - Title: "11-12", 1977; cuid22927 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0002)
      Alternate title: "11 thru 12"
      Credit info: Andrea Callard
      Capacity: 20 minutes
      Annotations: "11 thru 12" Andrea Callard c. '77 // 78 MM 283 // AC Box 37 NYC 10013
    - Title: Pus Factory - MASTER, 1984; cuid22928 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0003)
      Alternate title: Pus Factory
      Annotations: Pus Factory -- MASTER 1984 26 sec. B+W Use black and white part of color bars. 10 secs of black between bars and beginning of tape.
    - Title: Pus Factory - DUB, 1984; cuid22929 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0004)
      Annotations: "Pus Factory" c. Andrea Callard 1984 B+W Silent 26 sec. + credits DUB Box 37 10013 212-925-8974
    - Title: Pus Factory - DUB, 1984; cuid22930 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0005)
      Annotations: "Pus Factory" c. Callard 84 DUB 26 sec.
    - Title: Pus - Elements, [1984]; cuid22931 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0006)
      Alternate title:
      Credit info:
      Annotations: Callard - Pus Elements
    - Title: Notes on Ailanthus, cuid22932 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0007)
      Alternate title: Notes on Ailanthus - Visual Excerpts From Rough-Cut
      Annotations: Notes on Ailanthus / Visual excerpts from rough-cut. Transferred from Super-8 10 mins. (No sound) Andrea Callard Box 37 NYC 10013 925-8974-1247
    - Title: Landing #2B, cuid22933 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0008)
      Annotations: LANDING #2B
    - Title: Landing #1B, cuid22934 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0009)
      Annotations: Landing - #1B
    - Title: Moduretic, [Dub 9/2/1980]; cuid22935 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0010)
      Alternate title: M,S,+D "Moduretic"
      Credit info: Elaine Millaire
      Annotations: M,S,+D "Moduretic" Elaine Millaire 17:70 Dub 9/2/80 (written in pencil:) "narrator: 2 tks; 2 versions; [not vi bg]?"
    - Title: Untitled, cuid22936 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0011)
      Annotations: N/A
    - Title: [1]-- Drawers [2]-- Fragments of a Self Portrait, [circa 1975]; cuid22937 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0012)
      Format: 1/2 in. Open Reel
      Capacity: [20 minutes]
      Annotations: "Drawers" 15 min. // at slip of paper...#1 "Fragments of a self-portrait." 3 1/2 min. cut. Andrea Callard 617 Tyrone Drive Mincie, Indiana 47304. (Paper bookmark w/ annotation:) "sample #2 begins"
    - Title: [Gary Brown - Cal Arts], Unknown; cuid22938 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0013)
      Capacity: 30 minutes. 370m., 1210 feet
      Annotations: (On cardboard sleeve:) "Gary Brown" Cal Arts
    - Title: Fragments, 1974; cuid22939 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0014)
      Annotations: [On container:] Callard 925-8974 Umbrellas, etc. [On reel:] Callard '74 Fragments S.P.
    - Title: Drawers - MASTER, 10/16/1975; cuid22940 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0015)
      Alternate title: Drawers
      Annotations: [On contaier:] Drawers (M) 16 Oct. '75 [On reel:] d. MASTER -- blank
    - Title: Bechet, Smith, A.C. '74, 1974; cuid22941 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0016)
      Annotations: [On reel:] Bechet, Smith, A.C. '74
    - Title: [1]-- Drawers [2]-- Garbage, [1]-- 1975 [2]-- Unkown; cuid22942 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0017)
      Annotations: Drawers // Garbage
    - Title: [1]-- Drawers [2]-- Fragments of a Self Portrait, [circa 1975]; cuid22943 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0018)
      Annotations: "Drawers," 15 min. Andrea Callard c. // "Fragments of a Self Porttrait" (#1, 3 1/2 min. cut) COPY
    - Title: [Cara Perlman], Unknown; cuid22944 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0019)
      Annotations: [On container:] Cara Perlman 40 Lispenard St. #925-1013 *start this tape at 080
    - Title: Multisensory Teaching of Reading at the Mary Mc Dowell Center for Learning, 1999, cuid22945 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0020)
      Format: VHS
      Capacity: 30 minutes
      Annotations: Multisensory Teaching of Reading at the Mary Mc Dowell Center for Learning, 1999. (handwritten: Return to LUKE Geller/ Andrea Callard
    - Title: Jeff McMahon 231, cuid22946 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0021)
      Capacity: 120 minutes
      Annotations: (taped to cassette) 231 Jeff McMahon
    - Title: Untitled, cuid22947 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0022)
      Annotations: (No annotations)
    - Title: Lenora Helm's Workshops, cuid22948 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0023)
      Annotations: Lenora Helm's Workshops
    - Title: A.C., cuid22949 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0024)
      Annotations: (written on piece of masking tape on cassette:) "AC"
    - Title: Nutrition, cuid22950 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0025)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Nutrition
    - Title: Italian Cooking, 12/6/1992; cuid22951 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0026)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Italian Cooking 12/6/92
    - Title: [1]--Brooms [2]-- Willie and Luke [3]-- Sophie Dancing [4]-- My Lunch with Willie and Luke [5]-- Toys - Boat, Chairs, [1990] [1]--2/8 [2]-- 3/28 [3]-- 3/29 [4]--4/? [5]-- 6/?; cuid22952 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0027)
      Annotations: Feb 8 - "Brooms" Willie [Luke]; Mar 28 Willie and Luke; Mar 29 Sophie Dancing; Apr-"My Lunch with Willie and Luke" June - Toys - Boat, Chairs N. Peck
    - Title: KOBLA 12/19/02, 12/19/2002; cuid22953 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0028)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) KOBLA 12/19/02
    - Title: Bryant Lake Camp, cuid22954 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0029)
      Capacity: [15 minutes]
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Bryant Lake Camp
    - Title: Bryant Lake Camp 1993, cuid22955 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0030)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Bryant Lake Camp 1993
    - Title: Bryant Lake Camp - Video Yearbook 1994, cuid22956 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0031)
      Capacity: 10 minutes
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Bryant Lake Camp - Video Yearbook 1994
    - Title: [#1], cuid22957 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0032)
      Annotations: (on sleve:) 3 (crossed out) 1
- Series X: Audio recordings
  Audio materials consist of production elements for media works by Callard and documentation of works by others. Access copies may not be available yet. Please check with the Fales Archivist.
  - Subseries A: Audio elements
    Audio elements have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
    - Title: 2 A's Singing; Spring 1976, cuid22958 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0033)
      Format: 1/4 in. reel to reel
      Capacity:
      Annotations: (on container:) 2 A's Singing / '76 Spring
    - Title: A + C Sentence and Song Collection; Feb. 1, 1977, 2/1/1977; cuid22959 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0034)
      Annotations: (on container:) Side 1 A+C 1 Feb. '77 45 mn 71/2 Sentence and Song Collection
    - Title: A + C Sentence Collection #2, [1977]; cuid22960 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0035)
      Annotations: (on container:) A + C Sentence Coll #2
    - Title: Unititled, Unknown; cuid22961 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0036)
    - Title: Songs (1), Unknown; cuid22962 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0037)
      Annotations: (on reel:) Songs (1)
    - Title: Lost Shoe Blues, Unknown; cuid22963 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0038)
      Alternate title: 2 A's Singing; Spring '76
      Annotations: (on container:) Lost Shoe Blues [sung] July 5,'76 /// (on reel:) 2 A's Singing/ 76 Spring
    - Title: Bells, Unknown; cuid22964 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0039)
      Annotations: (on container and reel:) Bells
    - Title: The Double X Corporation Menaton, 2/1974; cuid22965 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0040)
      Annotations: (on container:) "The Double X Corporation Menaton" [Rene] William Feb 1974 1/4 track 71/2
    - Title: Thin Waxed Beekman, 10/1974; cuid22966 (Box 21, Folder 156.0041A)
      Annotations: (on container:) "Thin Waxed Beekman" 10/74 R.W. 71/2 ips 1/4 track
    - Title: Life Mixing, 7/5/1975; cuid22967 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0042)
      Annotations: (on container:) Life Mixing 7/5/75 1/4 tr dub 3 3/4
    - Title: Your Copy, Unknown; cuid22968 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0043)
      Annotations: (on container:) "Your Copy" 7 1/2 1/4 tr. 4 shortpieces
    - Title: "Double X": Winter Activity '74, [7/1975]; cuid22969 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0044)
      Annotations: (on container:) "Double X": Winter Activity '74 // Music in X pattern for Andrea (crossed out: "5/75) 7/75 7 1/2 1/4 Tr. Improvised, Buchla
    - Title: Music For Andy From Roberta For Her Quarter Century B-Day, Unknown; cuid22970 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0045)
      Annotations: (on container:) Music For Andy From Roberta For Her Quarter Century B-Day // speed 3 3/4
    - Title: Music in Loop Patterns for Andrea 7/75, 7/1975; cuid22971 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0046)
      Annotations: (on container:) Music in Loop Patterns for Andrea 7/75 Side 1 with voice loop Theresa / Side two Fast, Modular, America, improvised, Buchla, 7 1/2, 1/4 track
    - Title: Untitled, Unknown; cuid22972 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0047)
      Annotations: (no annotations)
    - Title: Debriefing: A Reading by Susan Sontag, 5/27/1979; cuid22973 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0145)
      Format: LP
      Capacity: Unknown
      Annotations: Debriefing: A Reading by Susan Sontag.
    - Title: Ambient #1: Music For Airports - Brian Eno, 1978; cuid22974 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0146)
      Annotations: Ambient #1 Music For Airports Brian Eno PVC 7908 (AMB 001)
    - Title: Y Pants: Beat It Down, cuid22975 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0147)
      Credit info: Producer: Wharton Tiers
      Annotations: Y Pants: Beat It Down
    - Title: Tunings: R. Buckminster Fuller, cuid22976 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0148)
      Annotations: R. Buckminster Fuller Tunings
    - Title: Electronic Parrot, Unknown; cuid22977 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0048)
      Format: Audiocassette
      Capacity: 90 minutes
      Annotations: (on container:)Electronic Parrot / (on cassette:)Side 1: Reese visits Paul DeMarinas + his Electronic Parrot and makes a letter to Andrea accompanied by Mozart // Side 2: The Electronic Parrot at Work
    - Title: Except That They Are Rocks '78, [1978]; cuid22978 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0049)
      Annotations: (on container and cassette:) except that they are rocks / 78
    - Title: G.B. Songs; 9/1974, cuid22979 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0050)
      Annotations: (on container:) G.B. Songs 9/74 // (on cassette:) 1/ Pretty Ma (11/74) 2. The Way That You Are Mine (9/1974) 3. I Just Want To Bleed
    - Title: Andrea Singing Spring '76 Into New Songs Spring '77, 1976-1977; cuid22980 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0051)
      Annotations: (on container:)Field Guide To Birds // (on cassette:) Andrea Singing Spring '76 into New Songs Spring Spring '77
    - Title: Win + Dan 1973, 6/21/1973; cuid22981 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0052)
      Annotations: (on container:) Win. Dan 73 // (on cassette:) Win + Dan Carol + Reese 6-21-73
    - Title: Questions, Messages, and Jazz, Unknown; cuid22982 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0053)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Questions Messages + Jazz
    - Title: Beached in Villages of Mobile Homes; 1977, cuid22983 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0054)
      Annotations: Beached in Villages of Mobile Homes; 1977 // Beached in a M.B.
    - Title: Heaven Rock Harp, Unknown; cuid22984 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0055)
      Annotations: (on container:) Terry Fox Various Excerpts // (on cassette:) Heaven Rock Harp
    - Title: Noise Fest, June 1981; cuid22985 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0056)
      Credit info: Executive producer: Joshua Baer
      Annotations: Noise Fest. (titles list in container)
    - Title: A.) MR 1/30/79 Hospital exp. B.) Musac, 1979; cuid22986 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0057)
      Annotations: (on cassette: ) A.) MR 1/30/79 Hospital exp. B.) Musac
    - Title: Doctor / Dentist Tape "79, 1979; cuid22987 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0058)
      Annotations: (on container:) Doctors + Dentist Tape Feb 79// (on cassette:) A. Callard c. Feb 1979
    - Title: Registration Fire Missions: High Burst Registration, Unknown; cuid22988 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0059)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Registration Fire Missions: High Burst Registration. Lesson #250-061-6334-E // TeleGeneral
    - Title: Circular Commotion #3, 1984; cuid22989 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0060)
      Annotations: Circular Commotion #3 //// c. 1984 Circle Arts, Inc.
    - Title: Red Rakes Wyoming, Unknown; cuid22990 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0061)
      Annotations: (on container:) Red Rake Wyoming // (on cassette:) Red Rake experiments / Wyom descriptions
    - Title: A Rambling, Unknown; cuid22991 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0062)
      Capacity: 45 minutes
      Annotations: (on container:) A Rambling // (on cassette:) 0-219 A Rambling Dear Carol…Health club
    - Title: Sun Ra 8/14/79 Squat thr, 8/14/1979; cuid22992 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0063)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Sun Ra 8/14/79 Squat thr
    - Title: Loop for Subway Hole (Winter '74), 1974; cuid22993 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0064)
      Annotations: (on container:) Loop for Subway Hole (Winter '74) 73-4 Loop noise for subway// (on cassette:) Some noise AC
    - Title: [1]-- Maritime Songs [2]-- Church Bells 1976 July 7, cuid22994 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0065)
      Capacity: 40 minutes
      Annotations: (on container:) Maritime Songs/ Church Bells 1976 July 7 // (on cassette:) Side 1: Maritime Songs Side 2: Church Bells
    - Title: [1]-- F.K. Song Gift '77 [2]-- Sawing, 1977-1978; cuid22995 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0066)
      Annotations: (on container:) F.K. song gift 77; Sawing // (on cassette:) Side A: Some songs for Andrea from Fred 1977 Side B: Saw Sounds from A. Dec 2, 1978
    - Title: [1]-- Alanthus Reading [2]-- A Talking Ailanthus, Unknown; cuid22996 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0067)
      Annotations: (on cassette) Side A: Alanthus reading Side B: A talking Ailanthus
    - Title: 11 thru 12 Sound Copy, [1977]; cuid22997 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0068)
      Alternate title: 11-12: gloves, bunk beds, electricity, small thoughts bogged down
      Annotations: (on container:) 11-12 / gloves - bunk beds - electric - bogged down - sm. thots // (on cassette:) A: A/R Cassette Test May '77 - gloves, bunk beds, electricity, small thoughts, bogged down
    - Title: Radio Music, Unknown; cuid22998 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0069)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Radio Music
    - Title: AC Wild Bill, Unknown; cuid22999 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0070)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) AC Wild Bill
    - Title: Untitled, Unknown; cuid23000 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0071)
      Annotations: No annotations
    - Title: Monica at Senate 12-21-7?, [197?]; cuid23001 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0072)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) 0-402 Monica at Senate 12-21-7?
    - Title: Ideal Bathtub Words, Unknown; cuid23002 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0073)
      Capacity: 45 miutes
      Annotations: (on container:) Ideal Bathtub // (on cassette:) A: 0-177 Hello Ideal Bathtub Words / b: Goodnight - 55 GB to RW then, Mack meets Lois
    - Title: Field Guide to Birds, Unknown; cuid23003 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0074)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Field Guide to Birds // Callard, A.
    - Title: [1]-- Bruised Knees [2]-- Radio Africa, Unknown; cuid23004 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0075)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) A: bruised knees B: Radio Africa
    - Title: [Hunniy; Keep Crying], Unknown; cuid23005 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0076)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) 1: [hunniy] 2: Keep Crying 1/2 Way
    - Title: [1]-- A Talking Ailanthus [2]-- Word Notes 5, May '77 [3]-- Auto-Bio-Underwater '77, 1977; cuid23006 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0077)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) A: A Talking Ailanthus // A: Word Notes 5, May '77 / B: Auto-Bio-Underwater '77
    - Title: Untitled (Endless Tape), Unknown; cuid23007 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0078)
      Capacity: 60 seconds
      Alternate Title:
    - Title: Untitled, Unknown; cuid23008 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0079)
    - Title: Fresh, Unknown; cuid23009 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0080)
      Annotations: (on container:) [sent by] Susan Stoltz 495 Broome Street NYC 10013 [mailed to:] Andrea Callard Bullard Mills Center South William St. Malone, NY 12950 // (on cassette:) Fresh
    - Title: Chris and Sue Jones; Winter '73, 1973; cuid23010 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0081)
      Annotations: (on container:) C/S Jones 73 // (on cassette:) A: Chris + Sue Jones had no heat one night and came over to sleep, drink wine + tell stories. Winter '73 B: C Jones Generally Boring
    - Title: [1]-- Chinese New Year 2/1974 [2]-- Painting Paper, cuid23011 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0082)
      Annotations: (on container:) Chinese New Year/ Paint Paper 74 // (on cassette:) 1:) 0-221 Chinese New Year, A Walk Thu 2/74 / 2:) Painting Paper
    - Title: Williams - Venetian Room, Unknown; cuid23012 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0083)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) 1: Notes from Ventitian Room - Ideas obsolete + [scapped] already unfortunately. / 2: Interview at the Venitian Room With Irregular Clock and [Ideal] Garden
    - Title: JVC - Demo tape, Unknown; cuid23013 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0084)
      Annotations: (on container:) JVC Demo -- Walon Jennings Dolly Parton, etc. / (on cassette:) JVC Demonstration Tape (orchestra selections)
    - Title: [1]-- Chanteuse; A Singing Evening with Sally White [2]-- Mitch Corber- Infinitessimus; a New Op-Op Opera, [1]-- 7/1983 [2]-- 1984; cuid23014 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0085)
      Annotations: (on container) Chanteuse; A Singing Evening with Sally White / Mitch Corber- Infinitessimus; a New Op-Op Opera // (on cassette:) Sally White at Tin Pan Alley w/ Mitch at elec.piano
    - Title: [1]-- Finch Mech; Birds [2]-- Dishes, Unknown; cuid23015 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0086)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Side 1: Finch Mech "Birds" / Side 2: Dishes
    - Title: Tounge + Groove '76 - fragment, 1976; cuid23016 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0087)
      Annotations: (on container:) fragment tongue + groove '76 / (on cassette:) I hv torchured some of the toungs
    - Title: Consumer Blues '77 - fragment, Unknown; cuid23017 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0088)
      Annotations: (on container:) fragment consumer blues '77 / (on cassette:) photo consumer/ b.queen (garb)
    - Title: Struk By Trucks, 7/ 1979; cuid23018 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0089)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Struk by Trucks 2:45 / July 79
    - Title: [Krank], Unknown; cuid23019 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0090)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) [KRANK]??
    - Title: Friday at Clarissa's; Feb. 18, 1983, 2/18/1983; cuid23020 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0091)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Friday at Clarissa's; Feb. 18, 1983 Side 1, Clarissa, Helga, Susan and later Trisssy / Side 2 - Helga, Clarissa, Trissy, Susan
    - Title: [1]-- Score for a Lunch [2]-- Dora Reese + Bob Dylan Enjoy Queen at Siberia…, Unknown; cuid23021 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0092)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Side 1: Score for a Lunch / Side 2: Dora Reese + Bob Dylan Enjoy Queen at Siberia 10 Cent Show
    - Title: Untitled, Unknown; cuid23022 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0093)
    - Title: AC Singing, Unknown; cuid23023 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0094)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) AC Singing
    - Title: Street Noise '79, 1979; cuid23024 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0095)
      Capacity: 46 minutes
      Annotations: (on container:) Street Noise 79 / (on cassette:) A: "erase it" B: Street Noise
    - Title: [1]-- Jackie Song [2]-- Drive Drivel; 1974, cuid23025 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0096)
      Annotations: (on container:)Jackie song-Drive drivel 74/(on cassette:)A:Some weird voice I heard driving thru Colo.In somebody else's florist truck./ B:Winter '74 Jackie comes to visit + we sing some oldtime songs
    - Title: [1]-- Driving Drivel '74 [2]-- Vermonters talking…, 1974; cuid23026 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0097)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) 1. Eric-VT. Vermonters talking about it. Winter'74. J Morse,Rachel, Eric // 2: May'74 Brief driving Drivel + Duet of selves + Nov '74 Additives Last 243 #'s.
    - Title: [1]-- Inter Pyrex…1974 [2]-- Sunday Filler, Youngblood, Big Wheel, cuid23027 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0098)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) A: Inter Pyrex Vibrational Action Feb '74 // B: Jan '74, Sunday [Filler], Youngblood, Big Wheel
    - Title: Leon in Muncie, Coffee; Summer '73, 1973; cuid23028 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0099)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) A: Leon in Muncie Coffee: Summer 73 // B: Most Garbage don't bother
    - Title: [1]-- Bear Mountain [2]-- Air View of Siberia, Unknown; cuid23029 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0100)
      Annotations: (on container:) Bear MTN/ Siberia // (on cassette:) 0-222 Bear Mountain -373 air view of Siberia
    - Title: Solo exploration of Telluride, Colorado - circa 1973, 1973 or 1974; cuid23030 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0101)
      Annotations: (on container: Colorado 73 or 4 // (on cassette:) Solo exploration of Telluride, Colo.
    - Title: Road Words, Unknown; cuid23031 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0102)
      Annotations: (on container:) Road Words // (on cassette:) Road Thoughts poetic 4-5 / burned arm-road jet trail-highway from air plane
    - Title: [1]-- Brick Howls Household - sound collection [2]-- Pulminary Disruptions, Al Libke, Unknown; cuid23032 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0103)
      Annotations: (oncassette:) Brick Howls household sound collection // B: Pulminary Disruptions, Al Libke
    - Title: Street Noise, Unknown; cuid23033 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0104)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) A: Street noise (crossed out "F/A Sound") // B: Street Noise